<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>York County Astronomical Society on </title>
    <link>https://ycas.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in York County Astronomical Society on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ycas.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>James Webb Space Telescope Talk</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/james-webb-space-telescope-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/james-webb-space-telescope-talk/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will host a virtual presentation at John C. Rudy Park Observatory December 11 at 7pm.
The evening will start with &amp;ldquo;The James Webb Space Telescope - a new cosmic journey begins&amp;rdquo; with Dr. Swara Ravindranath from the Space Telescope Science Institute in Baltimore, MD, discussing, via Zoom, the telescope&amp;rsquo;s key science goals. The presentation is outside in the Red Pine and White Pine pavilions using a large projection screen system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public StarWatch</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will host a Public Starwatch event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, December 11th 2021, at 8:00PM to 10:00PM to view the night sky through our telescopes.
Expand your mind by taking in the expanse of the universe. Come listen to a screen astronomical presentation on the current night sky, and a variety of astronomical topics, then view the December skies with us through one of our telescopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Radio Astronomy</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>Radio Astronomy, Solar Observing and Weather, and Telescope Clinic at Astronomical Society The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will be offering a public event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, May 21st, 2022, Solar and Radio Astronomy from 11:00AM - 3:00PM, and Telescope Clinic from 1:00PM - 2:00PM.
Society member Kerry Smith will be presenting the radio astronomy portion of the event as well as giving attendees a peek into the future of the Society&amp;rsquo;s radio astronomy endeavors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YLC Planetarium Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-shows/</guid>
      <description>All shows are cancelled until the Covid-19 virus is better controlled. Thank you for your understanding and stay safe.  The York County Astronomical Society, celebrating 15 years offering planetarium programs to the public, now offering Saturday evening programs for older family members at the York Learning Center Planetarium.
For more information on events, scheduling a private party star watch, directions to the observing site, or for general Society information please contact us at info@astroyork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Telescope</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</guid>
      <description>COMING NEXT SUMMER TO THE YCAS OBSERVATORY A 4.5 METER RADIO TELESCOPE
This year is going to be exciting for YCAS as we unveil our 4.5 meter radio telescope. It has been a three year project in the making collaborating with with the York County Parks, York College of Pennsylvania and the York County Astronomical Society (YCAS).
The radio telescope will be totally automated, fully steerable, tracking and web accessible instrument.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/donate/</guid>
      <description>Make a donation to YCAS
Formed in 1989, the York County Astronomical Society, a 501( c )(3) non-profit organization, aims to promote interest, public education, and advancement of the science of astronomy.
Have you attended one of our Public Events?
Astronomy Day?
The Lunar Eclipse?
Our Monthly Observing Sessions?
New Telescope Clinic?
Planetarium Shows?
Did you have a good time?
Did you learn something new?
If so, please consider a donation to YCAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society The York County Astronomical Society is a non-profit organization dedicated to the advancement of the science of astronomy.
The York County Astronomical Society was started in 1989, and currently has about 30 members in 4 counties in Pennsylvania.
The Society also has special programs to showcase eclipses, meteor showers, comets, and other special events.
The Society operates the York Learning Center Planetarium bringing astronomy to the public, presenting astronomical shows and related astronomy programs of the night sky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/gallery/</guid>
      <description>YCAS member Jim Smailing has taken some excellent pictures of the eclipsing Moon. These pictures were taken with the combination of a Motorola E5 plus cellphone, a Vankey cellphone telescope adapter mount, and an Orion ultrascopic 5mm eyepiece all attached to an Orion Skywatcher 120 f/8 acromatic refractor on an EG-3 equatorial mount with an Orion EQ-3M single axis drive. The first six photos were taken with a #15 yellow glass filter attached to the eyepiece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Events</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/upcomingevents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/upcomingevents/</guid>
      <description>*
 December 11 7pm to 8pm James Webb Space Telescope Talk at Rudy Park
 December 11 8pm to 10pm Public StarWatch at Rudy Park
 January 8 8pm to 10pm Public StarWatch at Rudy Park
 February 12 8pm to 10pm Public StarWatch at Rudy Park
 March 12 8pm to 10pm Public StarWatch at Rudy Park
 April 9 8pm to 10pm Public StarWatch at Rudy Park</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/join-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/join-us/</guid>
      <description>YCAS DUES ONLINE
Existing members of York County Astronomical Society can make dues payments at bottom of this page.
ATTENTION NEW MEMBERS
If you are mailing in your YCAS Membership application, please make sure it includes your email address so we may contact you, confirm your information, and invite you to our Yahoo! group.
If you are paying via PayPal, please make sure you click this link to send us an email once you complete your PayPal transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/resources/</guid>
      <description>Resources 
Pennsylvania, Maryland, Delaware, Virginia Astronomical Clubs   AELC - Astronomy Enthusiasts of Lancaster County  Astronomical Society of Harrisburg&amp;nbsp;  Amateur Astronomers Association of Pittsburgh  Berks County Amateur Astronomical Society  Central Pennsylvania Observers  Cherry Springs Dark Sky Fund/Association  Chesmont Astronomical Society  Cumberland Astronomy Club  Goddard Astronomy Club  Greater Hazleton Area Astronomical Society  Harford County Astronomical Society  Howard Astronomical League  Lackawanna Astronomical Society  Lehigh Valley Amateur Astronomical Society  NOVAC Northern Virginia Astronomy Club  Oil Region Astronomical Society  Penn State Astronomy Club  Starlight Astronomy Club Web Site  Westminster Astronomical Society  Tri-State Astronomers&amp;nbsp;  Kanawha Valley Astronomical Society  Star Parties  Almost Heaven Star Party  Black Forest Star Party  Cherry Springs Star Party  NOVAC Star Gaze  Staunton River Star Party  Other Related Astronomical Links  Aurora Solar Terrestrial Dispatch  Arkansas Sky Observatory  Astro Pix  Astronomical League   Astronomy Now Online  Astronomy Magazine  Astronomy Picture of the day  American Astronomical Society  American Association of Variable Stars  Association of Lunar and Planetary Observers  AstroMart  BAA Comet Section Home Page  Bad Astronomy  Black Forest Star Party  Cherry Springs  Constellations and their Stars  Gary&amp;nbsp;W.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Directions</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/directions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/directions/</guid>
      <description>York Learning Center Planetarium York Learning Center Planetarium on Google Maps From Route 30 take George street and head south towards downtown York and turn left on 6th Avenue (You will see a sign that says Elite Staffing Service at the turn to 6th Avenue) take 6th Avenue and you will come to one stop sign, continue on 6th Avenue up a slight hill and you will see the school on left at Elk street, from 6th Ave after passing Elk St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planetarium Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/planetariumshows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/planetariumshows/</guid>
      <description>All shows are cancelled until the Covid-19 virus is better controlled. Thank you for your understanding and stay safe.  Private Show Reservation Information The planetarium seats 60 people. Private programs are offered by reservation any day. School/Summer Camp groups can schedule during school hours Monday through Friday. The cost of a 45 minute program is $40, an additional hour is $30 ($70 total). There are some shows with a surcharge of $30 because they are streamed from a vendor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>