<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ycas.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/laser-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/laser-shows/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society, celebrating 19 years offering planetarium programs to the public, now offering laser shows for a limited time at the York Learning Center Planetarium.
The planetarium is located in the York Learning Center at 301 East 6th Avenue, York PA.
Admission is $15.00 for each person. Cash and most credit and debit cards are accepted. Online ticket sales are available on our Cur8.com page. The site charges a non-refundable fee of about $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StarWatch</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/starwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/starwatch/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will host a Starwatch event at their Observatory at John Rudy County Park, on the second Saturday of the month, at 7:00PM to 9:00PM to view the night sky through our telescopes.
Expand your mind by taking in the expanse of the universe. Come view the evening sky with us through one of our telescopes. Let our experienced members guide you on a tour of celestial wonders, including stars, and nebulae.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YLC Planetarium Childrens Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-childrens-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-childrens-shows/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society, celebrating 19 years offering planetarium programs to the public, now offering Saturday afternoon and evening programs at the York Learning Center Planetarium.
Saturday, December 6, 2025  2:00PM - One World, One Sky: Big Bird&amp;rsquo;s Adventure (pre-K to 1st grade)
 2:40PM - StarWatch
 3:20PM - Mars: The Ultimate Voyage (4th to 8th grade)  The planetarium is located in the York Learning Center at 301 East 6th Avenue, York PA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YLC Planetarium Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-shows/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society, celebrating 19 years offering planetarium programs to the public, now offering Saturday afternoon and evening programs at the York Learning Center Planetarium.
Saturday December 6, 2025  7:00PM - Chasing the Ghost Particle
 7:40PM - StarWatch
 8:20PM - Cosmic Castaways
  The planetarium is located in the York Learning Center at 301 East 6th Avenue, York PA. Admission is $4.00 for adults, $3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astrophotography</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/astrophotography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/astrophotography/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) has an active group of members doing astrophotography where they share their experience and joy of the hobby.
The Andromeda galaxy is located near the constellation of Cassiopeia. This Photo of the Andromeda Galaxy (M31) was taken with Wiliam Optics GT71 and William Optics FTL 91 scopes and the ZWO ASI 2600MC Astrophotography Camera. This composition was taken with 30 hours of exposures. Photo credit of Don Emmel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Telescope</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</guid>
      <description>THE YCAS OBSERVATORY A 3.5 METER RADIO TELESCOPE IS HERE!
We have first light.
This next year is going to be exciting for YCAS as we unveil our 3.5 meter radio telescope. It has been a six year project in the making collaborating with with the York County Parks, York College of Pennsylvania and the York County Astronomical Society (YCAS).
The radio telescope will be totally automated, fully steerable, tracking and web accessible instrument.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>