<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ycas.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Public StarWatch</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will host a Public Starwatch event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, July 11th 2020, at 8:00PM to 10:00PM to view the night sky through our telescopes.
Due to the pandemic, social distancing rules are enforced, masks are required for everyone at the event. The observatory is closed to the public. Telescopes will be brought out to the grass field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Radio Astronomy</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>Radio Astronomy, Solar Observing and Weather, and Telescope Clinic at Astronomical Society The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will be offering a public event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, July 25th, 2020, Solar and Radio Astronomy from 11:00AM - 3:00PM, and Telescope Clinic from 1:30PM - 2:00PM.
Society member Kerry Smith will be presenting the radio astronomy portion of the event as well as giving attendees a peek into the future of the Society&amp;rsquo;s radio astronomy endeavors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planetarium Closed</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/planetarium-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/planetarium-closed/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) has decided to close the planetarium until there is an effective and widely distributed vaccine available.
Thank you for your understanding and please stay safe.
For more information on events, scheduling a private party star watch, directions to the observing site, or for general Society information please contact us at info@astroyork.com or leave a voice message after the recording at 717 759-9227 or visit our Facebook page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Telescope</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</guid>
      <description>COMING NEXT SUMMER TO THE YCAS OBSERVATORY A 4.5 METER RADIO TELESCOPE
This and next year is going to be exciting for YCAS as we unveil our 4.5 meter radio telescope. It has been a three year project in the making collaborating with with the York County Parks, York College of Pennsylvania and the York County Astronomical Society (YCAS).
The radio telescope will be totally automated, fully steerable, tracking and web accessible instrument.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>