<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ycas.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Day StarWatch</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/earth-day-starwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/earth-day-starwatch/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will host a Earth Day and Lyrid Meteor Shower Starwatch event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Monday, April 22th 2019, from 8:00PM to 10:00PM.
The evening will begin with a screened astronomical presentation on current events and the April night sky. Guests will then be guided on a tour of the sky through one of the club telescopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Radio Astronomy</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>Radio Astronomy, Solar Observing and Weather, and Telescope Clinic at Astronomical Society The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will be offering a public event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, May 18th, 2019, Solar and Radio Astronomy from 11:00AM - 3:00PM, and Telescope Clinic from 1:00PM - 2:00PM.
Society member Kerry Smith will be presenting the radio astronomy portion of the event as well as giving attendees a peek into the future of the Society&amp;rsquo;s radio astronomy endeavors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>York Learning Center Planetarium Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/york-learning-center-planetarium-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/york-learning-center-planetarium-shows/</guid>
      <description>The Saturday March 2 Planetarium programs have been cancelled due to snow in the parking lot. The same programs will be shown April 6th.
The York County Astronomical Society, celebrating 13 years offering planetarium programs to the public, is now offering Saturday afternoon programs for young children and families and Saturday evening for older family members at the York Learning Center Planetarium. This month, we are featuring a children&amp;rsquo;s program, One World, One Sky: Big Bird&amp;rsquo;s Adventure and From Earth to the Universe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public StarWatch</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will host a Public Starwatch event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, March 9th 2019, beginning at 7:00PM.
The evening will begin with a screened astronomical presentation on current events and the March night sky. Guests will then be guided on a tour of the sky through one of the club telescopes. Attendees will be shown a host of celestial objects to include the crescent moon, globular clusters, the Andromeda galaxy and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>