<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ycas.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Public StarWatch</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-starwatch/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will host a Public Starwatch event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, April 8th 2023, at 8:00PM to 10:00PM to view the night sky through our telescopes.
Expand your mind by taking in the expanse of the universe. Come view the March skies with us through one of our telescopes. Let our experienced members guide you on a tour of celestial wonders, including stars, planets, nebulae and the Moon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Radio Astronomy</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/public-radio-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>Radio Astronomy, Solar Observing and Weather, and Telescope Clinic at Astronomical Society The York County Astronomical Society (YCAS) will be offering a public event at their Observatory at John C. Rudy County Park, 400 Mundis Race Road, York, on Saturday, April 15th, 2023, Solar and Radio Astronomy from 11:00AM - 3:00PM, and Telescope Clinic from 1:00PM - 2:00PM.
Society member Kerry Smith will be presenting the radio astronomy portion of the event as well as giving attendees a peek into the future of the Society&amp;rsquo;s radio astronomy endeavors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YLC Planetarium Afternoon Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-afternoon-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-afternoon-shows/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society, celebrating 17 years offering planetarium programs to the public, now offering Saturday evening programs for older family members at the York Learning Center Planetarium.
Saturday, May 6, 2023  2:00PM - One World, One Sky: Big Bird&amp;rsquo;s Adventure
 2:40PM - StarWatch
 3:20PM - Defying Gravity: It IS Rocket Science!  The planetarium is located in the York Learning Center at 301 East 6th Avenue, York PA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YLC Planetarium Shows</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/ylc-planetarium-shows/</guid>
      <description>The York County Astronomical Society, celebrating 17 years offering planetarium programs to the public, now offering Saturday evening programs for older family members at the York Learning Center Planetarium.
Saturday May 6, 2023  7:00PM - Forward! To the Moon
 7:40PM - StarWatch
 8:20PM - Hot and Energetic Universe
  The planetarium is located in the York Learning Center at 301 East 6th Avenue, York PA. Admission is $4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Telescope</title>
      <link>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ycas.github.io/post/radio-telescope/</guid>
      <description>COMING THIS SPRING 2023 TO THE YCAS OBSERVATORY A 4.5 METER RADIO TELESCOPE
This next year is going to be exciting for YCAS as we unveil our 4.5 meter radio telescope. It has been a five year project in the making collaborating with with the York County Parks, York College of Pennsylvania and the York County Astronomical Society (YCAS).
The radio telescope will be totally automated, fully steerable, tracking and web accessible instrument.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>